So, are you ready for a possible lockdown?
Are you ready for the possibility that the governments across the world might literally be like, you can't go nowhere?
Are you ready for this?
If you have pets, do you have food for them?
Do you have water?
Do you have extra gasoline?
Do you have rice?
So, what we're seeing right now, and I just posted this video on my page, okay?
I posted a bunch of heads of state around the world, from the Philippines to England to Australia and the United States, saying that there is an energy shortage that is coming among us.
Anytime that you see synergy of this type, you have to understand that it is not by coincidence, okay?
The other part of this is that the reason why there is synergy here, and that is because of the banking systems.
All of these countries have central banks that are controlled by the same families and the same system that are based in Switzerland.
So, when we look at like the Federal Reserve, when we look at the Bank of England, when you look at the IMF, the International Monetary Funds, even if a country doesn't have a central bank, if it has a loan with the World Bank or the IMF, it means that it is attached to the central bank.
So, whenever you see this cohesion, right, it lets you know that a message was passed down, and that's something that you can carry with you anywhere.
Anytime you see a cohesive message being sent, you being like dispersed, you can know that it came from an individual source.
And when I say cohesive message, I don't necessarily just mean like people who have the same values.
I mean like the language being the same.
And for what it's worth, Sarah Megatron, Canada is already in the mix of it.
They might change the same name, but Canada is part of the British Commonwealth, so they are already a part of this.
By the way, this is my cat, Sankara.
So, everyone say hi to Sankara.
There is a goal by people like Bill Gates to, by 2030, have a world that does not have an individual currency that is, sorry, to have a world that has one individual currency.
And that that currency is an electric currency.
And that ownership is no longer something that the ruling class is able to invest in.
That basically everything would be of value for rent.
Everything from your land, to your home, to your water, to your food.
Basically, there would be no ownership.
And we have seen this, for those of us who are millennials, in how even music has shifted.
Once upon a time, you could own your music.
This whole streaming shit, we didn't live that experience.
And don't get me wrong, there was a crossover time where you could download and play it as much as you want.
But you still owned it.
It still was in your possession.
Now, it's not the same.
And that is a part of a continued movement to move us out of the sense of possession.
Even when it comes to money, the lack of physical money being used is not by accident.
It is training us to be able to be controlled by a digital currency.
So, that is something that is foreseen in the future.
And what we are witnessing in the current present day is a continued effort to shut everyone down and take away freedoms, like Nicole said right here.
And, you know, COVID was the first attempt at this, right?
There had to be something created that would shut everybody down globally.
And you can say maybe it's a conspiracy theory or not.
However, the necessity to have theories about these conspiracies is absolutely real.
We need to have theories about these unexplainable phenomena because they are unexplainable.
No one can give a concrete reason for why.
So, we have to theorize.
And that theorizing is necessary because it keeps your brain sharp.
It keeps you asking questions.
And if you don't keep asking questions, we will literally all kill ourselves.
COVID was manufactured.
Period.
You cannot tell me it wasn't.
My girl, Nelsie.
You can't tell me COVID wasn't manufactured.
And anyone who has pattern recognition has to pay attention and see these things.
Because the fact that they are now announcing an energy shortage in the exact same way that they announced COVID should tell you something.
Jordi is jealous that I'm talking to y'all.
So, I'm asking you if you are prepared for a lockdown because it is very realistic that it could happen soon.
Yes, I believe cryptocurrency will be king.
Now, do I believe that these things will last forever?
No.
Because I do think that there's a hubris that we are witnessing.
Right?
I also, and if you don't know what hubris is, I want you to look it up.
H-U-B-R-I-S.
Yes, I want you to also remember that when COVID happened, you got to see that you did not have community.
Many people seem to think like, oh, but we always figure out community when we need it.
Huh?
People were literally fighting to not wear masks.
Like, I had a cold last week.
I still went to see my homegirl's baby today and kept the mask on.
Even after I started feeling better and I went out in the world, I put the mask on.
I understand people not wanting to wear a mask all the time.
However, on a basic level, it's like, if you're not feeling well, just wear the goddamn mask.
But folks don't even want to do that.
Folks were literally telling me that the revolution in Cuba is bullshit because there was not something,
because the people didn't get the revolution they fought for.
Someone's example was, well, you know, they made kids go out to rural areas to teach people how to read.
So when we're talking about the necessity to like have community, it's not something that is like, you know, some out here allegory.
We're going to find out in real time what it is.
And this next iteration of it will probably be very different than COVID because the limitations will be greater.
You see, in COVID, they couldn't stop you from driving.
It wasn't like, oh, we can keep you from going anywhere.
They needed us to still be driving.
They needed us to still be flying.
However, they are making concessions for that.
You already see that their air traffic control is non-existent.
You already see that TSA is non-existent.
And I'm saying non-existent, I'm being hyperbolic.
But what I mean by non-existent is that they really aren't caring about the efficacy of either of these agencies.
So that lets you know that flying is something that they are caring less and less about because they want to keep you in one place.
They want to make it harder for you to move around.
That makes it easier for them to extract your energy.
That makes it easier for them to incarcerate you.
Okay?
That makes it easier for you to be controlled.
That makes it easier for people to flip the F out.
That makes it easier for people to give the F in.
So I also want to ask you, like, what are you doing for yourself?
Did you talk to a tree today?
Did you walk outside today?
Did anything bring you joy today?
Because these things are really coming.
And someone said, please meet me at a library and we can have a read-off.
I don't know.
There's an argument happening in the chat.
Okay, extra.
They said, I talked to my dog.
H Montana said, I listened to the river the other day.
My little green space said, I planted seeds and planted flowers.
Y'all better do that.
BB said, I walked outside and the cops are already everywhere.
Okay, I didn't know it was going to go in that direction.
Ocean said, I made art or make art.
You better learn how to make joy where you're at.
You hear me?
Y'all better learn how to make joy where you're at.
This country has taught us that you need to consume in order to find joy.
You better learn how to make joy where you're at.
You got to do it.
And while we're at it, learn how to rub one out.
Some of y'all are not sleeping well.
Learn how to rub one out so you can get a good night's sleep.
I'm speaking to the women because the dudes already know this.
Get you a good night's sleep.
Get in touch with you.
You think I'm joking and I'm so serious.
I'm so serious.
Okay.
Real ones know.
I love this too, Kira.
They're doing this on Ring too.
I love how on Nextdoor people are posting what they need and others can comment if they have that item.
This is something that I think is really useful.
You know, don't get me wrong.
Some of these, well, I go ready.
If you don't understand what I'm talking about, then maybe you should be quiet because what I'm talking about all connects to each other.
So someone said masks are unhealthy.
Get them out of here.
So, you know, a lot of these Nextdoor, the Neighborhood app, et cetera, they have things like what's free in your neighborhood.
They have bartering sections, et cetera.
So these are very useful because, one, it allows you to have interaction with folks, even if you don't necessarily want to, like, go and sit in their house and hang out.
But it's still like, oh, you live here and I live here and you need that and I need that.
And it's just an extra little, it's an extra step to take, but it's a useful step.
And I will be the first to tell you that I need to do this.
I need to do this.
My mother be sending me a whole bunch of nonsense.
And I need to let people know, I possess this nonsense.
Do y'all want this?
Do y'all want this nonsense?
Like, for real.
Shout out to the person who said they've been walking two miles.
Yes, yes.
There is a very real impending lockdown coming.
For those who are just joining, I am speaking about the recent news that has been spreading across the world that there is an energy shortage.
This is a complete false scarcity.
There is no scarcity of energy.
None.
There is no scarcity.
There is no energy scarcity whatsoever.
There is an attempt to try to make it on a bad guy for saying, yeah, you can't come through unless you disassociate yourself with those people who've been doing the genocide forever.
And now somehow that is creating a scarcity of energy.
The Strait of Hormuz is closed.
Well, baby, the Strait of Hormuz was open.
And then you went and threw bombs in these people's life.
And so they closed it.
So all of this, though, if you're paying attention and you don't, and you've relieved yourself of the belief that the people who run the world have the world's people, have the best interests of the world's people.
Once you remove yourself from that, you're able to start looking at them like the shady mean girls at your school who plan for like months for what they're going to do at homecoming to fuck up somebody's day, except extend those months to years.
These people plan for years.
They're patient and they're able to be patient because they are usually very well supported financially and they're busy.
And so I thought I want a lot of people to take some time to look up 2030 project 2020, sorry, project 2030 and the one world order, because that's where we're headed.
That's where we're headed.
This idea that Mark J. W. D. said right here that we'll own nothing and be happy.
Paper money is about to be non-existent.
Yes.
You know, the thing about it, though, is that I really do believe that if people could just sharpen up, these people are not smarter than anybody.
They're not smarter.
They just have a tighter network and they're just more evil.
They're nefarious.
They're able to like lock in and do all of this like puppetry.
That's not my skill set.
I ain't gonna lie to you.
Dime lo.
So, you know, for someone like me, like, I really wish I could just go to a cash, a cash business.
Like, I hate that we only exist on the Internet.
It drives me bugged in crazy.
It drives me crazy.
Would I take money out the bank?
I mean, at this point, it feels like what's what's money in the bank going to mean?
Okay.
So these are just the things that I don't have the answers of what to do.
I'm just now realizing what is.
And I know some people feel like, well, don't tell me what it is if you can't tell me what to do.
And those are not my people.
Those are not my people.
I tell people what I'm hearing and what I'm learning so that there can be more than just me trying to figure out the solution.
Because I do not by any means think I am the only one who can come up with a solution.
One of the things I actually enjoyed about my ex, even though he's a ridiculous human being, was that our brains work differently.
So there would be times where, like, I just could not figure something out.
And I'd be like, yo, come here.
And I would, like, put him, like, this is what this is.
And then he'd be like, oh, what about this?
And I'd be like, never even occurred to me.
Never even occurred to me.
And, you know, that's what I think is the beauty about having different folks involved in the thinking and the ideating and the wonderment and the imagination around where we are and where we're going.
The other part of it is that, along with what you say here about, like, naming it and changing it, there's lies that are being continuously disseminated as magic.
So we have to tell the truth.
That's, like, the loudest thing we can do.
That's the easiest thing we can do.
Does any country on my radar seem prepared?
Well, I do think there's just lifestyles that are more prepared for that type of shutdown than others.
If you live on an island, you already basically understand what it is to be isolated.
You already have a consciousness around limits, right, around scarcity.
That's a different mindset and a different culture than a place like, you know, Europe and, you know, East Asia and the U.S.
where we're just embedded in hyper-consumerism.
So, you know, when I look at, like, the islands, you just have not only a culture that is more conscious around this,
but there's also a history and an internal indigenous knowledge that is aware of this.
So it's not to say that I think that there's, like, countries that, government-wise, are more prepared because they have, like, a committed consciousness that's going to attach to this.
But I do think there are people.
You know, for what it's worth, Cuba has been sanctioned and embargoed for over 60-something years, and they are rocking steady.
Rocking.
The UPS man is pulling up, and I really need to give him something.
But it's not prepared anyway, so I'll give it to him to another day.
So, any other questions?
It's nice to see so many of you all on the mindset of stewardship, land stewardship, you know, land, like, love of the land, regard for the land, awareness of the land.
And B.B. asked, how are you?
I mean, you know, I'm just trying to stay the course of my purpose without getting pulled in a million different directions, which is very easy to do.
And then I end up being purposeless.
Laurel, I am feeling so much better, and I am taking, was it Iman's advice of eating a spoonful of sugar every four hours to get this mucus out of here.
So, Ducks and Tigers, the songs got on pause because I was traveling and I was sick, but I have to get back to music.
I woke up out of my sleep last night and literally was like, you have to focus on the music.
So, I got to get back.
How do I manage not getting overwhelmed and burned out?
I get overwhelmed and burned out.
And then I just get back together.
And then I get it together.
But I get overwhelmed and burned out.
It just doesn't last like a long time, but it lasts and then it goes away.
Why are y'all talking about sugar?
I also like go swimming and I also go to the river.
Someone said I need to fast.
That's the quickest way to health.
I feel like people say that, but it's like varied.
It's so varied.
Like, is it a...
No, a spoonful of honey.
I said sugar.
Oh, because I was thinking a spoonful of sugar helps some medicine go down.
My fault.
Honey.
A spoonful of honey.
My bad.
I meant a spoonful of honey.
Swimming updates.
I found a new place to go swimming and I'm going to be checking them out in a few, like in next week.
Someone asked me better question.
Who are you supporting for governor?
Nobody.
I'm not supporting anybody for governor.
I miss being on set with you.
You were spitting in my space.
What do you mean?
Who is this?
The right Nikki?
Is this Nikki?
That's for Nikki.
Nikki from Insecure.
I just scared all of my cats.
Let me tell y'all something.
We would be in that trailer at Insecure and Nikki would be holding me down.
I remember the first day we had to put my wig on and Nikki was like, this ain't going to do it.
This is not...
I'm not sending you out there like that.
And the homeboys at Insecure that kept me sane.
That's who kept me sane.
The hairstylists and the homeboys.
When I was on Insecure, that was who kept me sane, man.
Because the rest of them broads was full of shit.
But them folks was the real ones and they kept me sane.
Absolutely.
So shout out to Nikki in here who also kept me fly.
And we had gotten my wig installed so bada bing bada boom that I didn't have to show up at 4.30 a.m.
for a 7.30 on camera call.
Y'all.
We said no, ma'am.
Nikki said, here's what we're going to do.
We're going to braid you down and we're just going to keep that braid down.
Okay.
And then you can just come here and we're just going to plop it on.
So, blah!
They had me coming at 4.30 a.m. for a 7.30 on camera call.
Do you understand?
And the first day back on season five, I was driving to set and it was 4.30 a.m.
And I drove by a car that had spun off the road at the separation of the 110 and the 5.
And I like pulled over because clearly somebody got in an accident.
So, I pull over and I run to the side of her car and it's a young lady.
It's a sister.
And she's like, my arm!
And I was like, oh my God.
Okay.
So, I'm calling 911.
I'm calling 911.
And I'm like, yo, I am located at the diversion between the I-5 and the I-10 coming off the 101.
This woman just spun out of her car.
I mean, she just spun off the highway in her car.
She clearly has a broken arm.
And 911's like, wait, I don't understand.
Where are you?
Oh my God.
I literally just told you exactly where I am.
Exactly.
Well, I mean, I just can't understand.
I said, ma'am!
Ma'am!
I need you to get with me.
I need you to get with me because this person is in a vehicle and they are hurting.
So, I got the woman together and she was like, all right, we're sending an ambulance.
Now, a car pulls up and these two brothers get out the car and they was like, you know,
you good?
You good?
And I was like, it seems like she has a broken arm.
So, now I turn back to her and she goes, let's see you!
Love you too!
That girl!
Ma'am!
We gotta get you good!
But you know what's crazy?
You know what I'm sitting here thinking in my head?
I'm gonna miss my call time.
These motherfuckers already be on some weird shit and now I'm gonna miss my call time.
So, I had to text and be like, listen, a lady, I pulled over because I saw a car accident
on the side of the road and so I'm running behind.
And so, I turned to the brothers who were clearly nation and I was like, are you, I said,
what are y'all doing?
And they said, we're gonna stay here till the ambulance comes.
And like, I had to feel their energy and they felt solid.
So, I was able to bounce.
The girl said, she was like, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
And I hope that she's okay to this day.
Someone asked, do I miss SUNY Purchase?
I do not miss SUNY Purchase.
However, I will be doing the commencement speech at Black graduation at Purchase College this
year and they will be giving out the Amanda Seals Activism Award again.
Um, so excited to be a part of that.
Um, but anywho, I just want to bring us back to asking you all questions about your, your,
your preparedness.
So, you know, those of you all who are on here, are you prepared for the event of being
locked down where you are not able to drive?
You're not allowed to drive.
Hendy, I'm not going to tell you where the lip is from because they didn't pay me to promote.
Are you prepared to be stuck at home again like COVID?
Are you mentally prepared to be stuck at home again like COVID?
They are preparing for this.
They're preparing for this.
How am I preparing?
Well, I really honestly just, I just realized this is happening.
So I've been preparing by stocking up on water.
Um, I've been preparing by stocking up on food for my pets.
Um, I've been preparing by getting a solar panel that can, um, charge a generator.
Um, I do need to do better about fuel.
I need to also better understand my generator.
Um, I am prepared with like candles because what they're going to do.
So I want to also let you all know that the lockdown is going to involve a false fuel scarcity.
So, you know how they're like making a fuel scarcity in Cuba?
If anyone has noticed that, did any of you guys see that there's been like a fuel scarcity
that was created in Cuba?
Because I was in Cuba and there literally was a blackout, right?
We legit did not have electricity.
So that right there is letting you know what they are capable of doing and what they will
do to people.
And many people seem to think that the United States will do one thing to one people, but
won't do it to themselves.
They literally created a blockade that prevented fuel from being sent to Cuba for three months.
They could not do surgeries.
NICUs could not run, um, electrics because the, because of the lack of fuel, they had
also an issue with the electrical grid.
These are real repercussions that were created solely by the imperialists of the world.
And I want to make sure that you all understand that oftentimes it gets just placed on the United
States, but there are other countries that comply with the United States, including the Caribbean.
Russia just sent a ship to Cuba with oil and it was made, it was allowed to go through.
That was the first time that they had an oil shipment in since, since December, since December
13th.
And what happens is that, okay, so we don't have oil, we'll use electricity, but the electrical
grid is not meant to run in that level of capacity.
So then it gets weakened and then it gets failed and then it fails.
And here we go.
There we go.
Like Florida girl said right here, anything they do to Palestinians, they will do to you.
I want y'all to understand that before there was Palestine, there was Ireland.
Before the, before the colonizers were practicing their surveillance, practicing their artillery on
the Palestinians, they were doing it on the Irish.
That's why there's such a connection between the Irish and, you know, I have to say it like
that every time, right?
That's why there's such a connection between the Irish and the Palestinians, because they
were the first.
There was no paper, there was no potato famine.
There was no reason, there was no, oh, we don't have potatoes.
We have to come to the, to the United States.
No, there was a blockade.
The English prevented food from being allowed to be sent into Ireland and thus they starved
the people of Ireland out.
Then they forced them to flee because less Irish people makes it easier to take your land
and sent them over here so they could be indentured servants, which is a version of slavery.
Oh my gosh, is that right?
King Darius 09, please go to international energy, international, what did he say?
International Energy Agency.
All right.
So the International Energy Agency, the IEA works with governments and industry to shape
a secure and sustainable energy future for all.
So that right there lets you know that they are foul, that they are foul.
Anything that says secure and sustainable energy future for all is foul because that's not
even what we're seeing in actionable ways.
We're not seeing an effort to make industry, sorry, we're not seeing an effort to make energy
secure and sustainable.
The concept of industry to do that is literally counterintuitive.
Are y'all still with me?
Let me know because I'm kind of cooking right now.
The concept of industry is literally about capitalism.
So it is counterintuitive to make something secure in capitalism because capitalism requires
scarcity.
And so if something is secure, then that means that it's not going to need to be replaced.
So therefore, when you hear anything that uses this type of language, it is a bunch of
jumbly, jumbly.
It's just jumbly, wumbly to make you think that it's legit when it's not.
The International Energy Agency works with governments.
Anytime you see that works with governments.
Well, we all know that governments, by and large, are controlled by a central banking system
that seeks only to hoard power by creating debt reliance.
And the people that are in power in government know that and they are put there to or in order
to keep perpetuating that.
So the IEA saying they work with governments just means that they actually are in cahoots
with governments.
That's what they're actually saying.
So if we're going to read this in a way that's actually real, the international, so it says the
International Energy Agency works with governments and industry to shape a secure and sustainable
energy future for all, what this really says is the International Energy Agency is in cahoots
with governments that perpetuate capitalism in order to continue reliance on false scarcity.
I mean, I'm doing this off the top of my head, but that's what that really means.
So someone said, okay, well, go to the IEA website because people are already, they're
already talking about on the website, like places that are shutting down their schools,
et cetera, et cetera.
So let's take a gander at some of these headlines over here.
Joint statement by the, joint, joint statement by the heads of the International IEA, International
Monetary Fund and World Bank Group.
So these are the people who are ruining the world and they've been ruining it for centuries.
It's not a mystery.
It's just that we get so distracted with the people that are right in front of us that these
people can continue to carry on and do what they do.
What did I tell you all at the beginning of this live?
What did I tell you about the bankers?
When you see the term international, it should concern you because essentially the world is
so different that there really is no, like there is no effective way for an agency to
operate internationally.
And there's no necessity for it to operate internationally unless it is trying to disperse, disseminate
an international goal.
And that international goal has continuously been colonialism.
It's just the expansion of the Roman Empire.
I answered your question, BB.
I don't even know what your question was, but I'm glad I answered it.
This is Lumumba.
How are you?
This is Patrice Lumumba.
He has a deformity in his back legs and in his front paws.
But boy, it does not hold him back.
He can run.
Do you want to get down?
So I'm going to read this to you.
The heads of the International Energy Agency, International Monetary Fund and World Bank
Group have agreed to form a coordination group to maximize their institutions response
to the energy and economic impacts of the war in the Middle East.
So this means that we are going to have a, we're going to have a global shutdown.
These people are so evil.
Y'all don't even understand.
Like when you talk about Democrats and Republicans, like if these people were really about anything,
that they would be standing up to this.
This is what they would be standing up to.
The Middle East war has caused major disruptions to live and livelihoods.
So, okay.
I want to disrupt a thought that you may have right now.
Now, it's very easy for you to look at countries that are dissing the U.S.
and be like, see, even Italy is not fucking with the U.S.
See, even Canada is not fucking with the U.S.
Again, I want to remind you, all these companies, I mean, all these, all these countries are companies.
All of these countries are part of a consortium that is controlled by the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund.
Thus, they will work in tandem and different folks will have different action items.
What I see, what I believe is happening is that there is a, what's being created is the fodder for a World War III that is impactful of everybody.
Yes, right now, it looks like it's just the U.S., Israel, and Iran.
However, what I look, what it looks like to me is that when we're watching all these other countries say, like, we have a fuel shortage, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera,
what they are saying without saying yet is this is because of the United States.
I believe that what we are witnessing is the fall of the United States for there to be a greater rise, a rise of a greater governing body, and that that fall is required.
And what's going to, I feel what we are watching is the descent into a war that will ideally, in their minds, make the entire world say, please save us, please save us.
And then they will be like, well, this is the only option, a new world order.
And I don't want you to be afraid of words like Illuminati and words like New World Order because you have been taught to believe that those things are kind of like made up, fantastical concepts, and they're not.
The word Illuminati is just Italian, so it sounds foreign to you because it's not English.
But at the end of the day, it's a real thing, and it's existed for a very long time.
The New World Order sounds phony to you because they even put it in wrestling, and they do that.
They put it in spaces that are considered fake, movies, entertainment, et cetera, so that you will not consider taking it seriously, so that it will become just like a kind of fantastical concept, or it will remove, you know, the, it will remove the efficacy of it, right?
So when you see things like NWO, you don't think of like an actual movement orchestrated by people at the top that you don't see.
Many of you think of wrestling, am I right?
Like, I don't even know about wrestling, but I know about NWO being a part of wrestling.
So, you know, like, sometimes I just feel like I'm telling you all this stuff because I don't want to just keep it in my own mind.
I also feel like it's just very necessary to see that there is an entire world that you, like, when they say it's a simulation, like, okay, Truman Show is like the literal,
Truman Show is the literal interpretation of the simulation, however, we are in a simulation, in that what we think is the world is not actually the world.
We think we live in a country that is sovereign, that makes independent decisions about how it moves on the planet, on the planet, and that's not true.
We think we have a bipartisan government of two opposing parties that fights back and forth for the betterment of their people.
That's not true.
We think that there is a grand distinction between the human form and trees, between the human body as nature and nature.
Like, that's just a few of the things that we have been taught to believe.
So, the movie, The Matrix, similar to Truman Show, is another example of the concept of simulation being placed into a...
Are you okay? Are you playing?
You guys playing?
Yes?
You're playing?
Oh my gosh, come here.
Nope, you're going to go back to play.
You're making a choice? What do you want to do?
You want to play over there? You want to play over here?
He doesn't know.
So, that's really, you know, what's going on.
You know, I see people saying, like, we should be done with Professor Shang because he's talking about the Freemasons, etc., etc.
And whenever I see folks that are so confident about not talking about those things, I know that they're just not ready yet.
They're not ready yet because it's much easier to keep your concept of the boogeyman to an image you've already conceptualized.
The more nebulous it becomes, the harder it becomes to fight.
So, a lot of folks don't want to expand their concept of the bad guy to include that which they have yet to be able to put a finger on.
So, the Epstein Files has really opened the door for many of us because it really shows you the actual finger on...
It really shows you the enemy in real time that you've been talking about.
So, where people may have thought, oh, this was nebulous, it's like, well, no, it's right here.
See? It's right there.
It's incredibly frightening to fight an enemy you can't see.
So, a lot of people will literally just stick to, well, Trump is the problem.
Or they will stick to the United States is the problem.
When it's much bigger than the Trump or the United States.
We don't know how many of us are even, like, real humans.
They cloned a...
They cloned a sheep.
Remember when they cloned Dolly the sheep?
In, like, the 90s?
You think if they was cloning sheep in the 90s, they ain't cloning humans yet.
That don't even make sense.
It just don't even make sense.
We gotta make sense.
They cloned a sheep dumb long ago, bro.
You know how far...
You know how long ago it'll be this way.
I hadn't even gotten my period yet and they had cloned a sheep.
I'm 45.
Henrock, that's not the point.
Trump is part of the problem.
But that's it.
Part.
You may have been part of the problem because you was running around behind Diddy for a long time.
Did you know about any of that weird shit going on?
Did you know he was beating Cassie ass while you was passing out records?
Because a lot of you niggas in this industry was doing a lot of turning your eye and turning the blind side while fuck shit was happening.
I don't think some of y'all understand how long I've been around.
Henrock known me since I was 22.
22.
I'm an old lady now.
And my locks need to be twisted.
Okay, so how do we prepare?
I mean, on a basic level, I want y'all to just think about how unprepared you were for COVID.
How would you do it differently now?
So I want you to start there.
If you had the opportunity to prepare for COVID, how would you do it?
I'll be 45 on July 1st.
How would you do it?
So start with that.
And don't just think about, like, food items.
Like, think about your mentals, right?
Like, think about the people around you.
You know, would you be able to walk to people's house?
You know, if you are immobile and you're disabled, how would you get access to that which you need for your welfare, right?
How would you, again, take care of your pets, your kids?
What are the ways in which you would manage if you had no electricity?
Who is this prick?
You need love and romance, too.
Not activism 24-7.
I get plenty of love.
I don't need romance right now.
I'm good.
Some people are like, okay, I worked from home.
Some of y'all are workaholics.
Let's be honest with ourselves.
If you didn't have the work to keep you engaged and distracted, what would you do?
What is the motive for the blackout?
The motive for a blackout that would affect the world is fear.
Here's what I'm trying.
You know how folks are like, we need to do a general strike.
They're going to do one on us first.
While everybody has been sitting around planning a strike, instead of just fucking doing it,
they will do it to us first.
And someone said, when?
You see, that's the trick.
You don't know when.
But you know it's coming if you're paying attention.
And, okay, someone said they don't need us anymore.
That I disagree with.
They always need us because they need a labor force.
They always need us.
So when I see people like, we're going to strike on May 1st.
We're going to strike on May 1st.
I'm like, really?
By the way, it's not we're going to start the strike on May 1st.
I want you to know that.
It's not that we're going to start the strike.
It's just we're going to strike on May 1st.
Do you think understanding the concept of energy frequency is important in conjunction?
Absolutely.
I'm trying to get better at understanding and learning, too.
There you have it.
Now, this is why I love talking with y'all because you bring in other concepts that I didn't even think of.
Jamila Hasamin said, we were able to connect virtually, but in an energy lockdown, I don't know how we would teach the babies.
How would we teach each other?
You know how much stuff people learned during COVID?
Not just baking bread.
And someone said, you know, this is starting.
It has to be after Easter.
You're not wrong.
Timing-wise, this is just like COVID.
All of this is happening in the same time frame as COVID.
All of it.
Yes, happy Tara.
When Trump said it on is going back to Stone Ages, he meant the world is.
Yes.
How would you contact others to organize without electricity?
We would have to get on foot and we would have to organize in person.
Bye, Zen Bedhead.
We need to remember how to write things down.
Which engages our brain better than typing, I learned.
Which doesn't surprise me, but I feel you, Jamila.
So I just wanted to talk to y'all because it always helps my brain work.
And I think it's also very important for y'all to know that you're not crazy and that there's other people who are thinking and seeing what you're seeing.
Someone said landline will work.
That is not true.
Landlines in many places don't even exist anymore.
They don't make landlines that aren't digital in many places.
For real.
So there's no such thing as a landline.
And that's also by design.
Walkie-talkies are a real thing.
You know, getting walkie-talkies that have rechargeable batteries are a real thing.
And, you know, we are in the midst of a full moon.
So if you haven't taken a full moon bath, this is a good time to do so.
To get centered and to kind of give your body some peace.
Look at Talia telling y'all right there, we used to have seekers and the receivers would be on the tribe.
And you would send somebody out, a seeker, and someone will go and look out for water, et cetera, and send back intel telepathically to the tribe.
Now, I don't think we ready at telepathic yet, but that's a very real thing.
I just saw someone in a group chat I'm in say, I'm so sorry we're not in a democracy anymore.
We were never in a democracy.
Why am I in that group chat?
Yeah, we need solar chargers and solar lanterns and a flint.
So I suggest everybody go to IEA.org and look up anything that you do not know or any organization, any agency that you have never heard of.
If you don't know what the International Monetary Fund is, then I want you to look it up.
If you don't know what the World Bank Group is, I want you to look it up.
If you don't know what the IEA is, I want you to look it up.
I want you to always read things, also thinking, what are they trying to convince me of in writing this?
Read everything skeptically.
What are they trying to convince me of in writing this?
What are they trying to manipulate me to do in writing this?
And it doesn't mean that you have to be riddled by paranoia.
I know that our thoughts are being heard.
I mean, it happens all the time where I think of something, I don't verbalize it at all, and then it shows up on my timeline.
And I'm just like, can y'all niggas get out of my head?
Because if you think about it, like, we can't see Wi-Fi.
We can't see radio waves.
However, we know they exist.
You are a combusting engine.
You are giving off energy.
You can't see it, but it exists.
You know it exists.
You feel other people's energy.
That energy is being mined by factions and by industries that you're not even aware of.
So, again, I want to remind everybody to ask yourself, what didn't I have enough of or what didn't I think about before COVID that I ended up actually, like, suffering from or that I was in lack of?
And that could be community, that could be dry goods, that could be water, all of these things.
Okay?
Start thinking in that way.
Start thinking in how you can use the training that you've already had.
Okay?
Someone asked, what independent media are talking about this?
You're here.
Y'all, be blessed.
Take a look at the post that I've put up today on my Instagram.
There's some really good information there.
Also, if you're considering joining a community that's about it, about it, make sure you check out my Patreon.
It's a $5 subscription.
And stay blessed.
Know that people have been on this planet for quite some time figuring it out.
And we will not let the evil take us out.
Mwah!